Grau Puche Recarens, designer and developer

email me at talk@graupuche.info · my website is graupuche.info · I have a blog blog.graupuche.info

24 year-old major in graphic design & web development skills, and a great focus on experiences. Both tangible and intangible. Specialized on these by pursuing a master's degree at NYU's Interactive Telecommunications Program. To study interaction as a subject, and more specifically HCI.

And got a deeper dive into fullStack web development. Building my own servers and making use of them for various projects, combining the web and physical interfaces.

Education

Spanish basic obligatory education (EPO & ESO) 2 year University Preparation Course on Science & Technology

BFA in Graphic Design

at ESDi, which is part of Universidad Ramón Llull (URL)

Master at NYU's

Interactive Telecomunications Program (ITP)

Language

English reading, writting & speaking - level C2

English certificates: FCE, CAE & CPE reading writting & speaking - level C2 Spanish Catalan reading writting & speaking - level C2

Capable of understanding spoken and written Italian and basic written German

Experience

Designer and Developer for Broadway window displays, fall 2017

Web designer/dev at Futtoc, during 2016

Office Staff

at MRW, during 2015 (courier service)

Retail Staff

at Companyia d'Alella, from 2014 to 2016

Check-in Agent

at Concierge BCN, from 2013 to 2015

Graphic Designer

at Sabem aquell que diu..., from 2013 to 2014

Administrative

at Puche Recarens S.L. from 2012 to 2013

Volunteer

at Foster Care Center "Casa Solaz", from 2010 to 2012

Skills

Microsoft Suite

Adobe Suite

Cinema 4D, Rhinocerous 3D, Fusion 360, 3D Printing Eagle, Bantam Tools

Arduino and similars

Throught hole board-making

Surface mount electronics

(electronics, soldering, fabrication ...) comfortable with power tools

html, css 3+ years exp.

javascript, node 3+ years exp.

C# 2 years exp.

Python I+ years exp.

Game Desing and Development experience. Video and photography skills (in & out of studio)

Fast Learner, Faster **Prototyper**

Exceptional sense for User experience

Good with short deadlines

Lookling for a fast paced work env.

End Note

I am what in the industry you would call a "creative Technologist" but I reather say that Im a highly creative person that has aquired and it's proficient in a variety of technical endeavours. That is way too long.

I'm a designer with a very techinal skillset, and I would say that this Resume does not make a good job at showing what I've been doing for the last couple of years. So please check out my website/blog (top of the page).